Guide to the New-York Historical Society Museum Department Records 1765, 1830-2018 NYHS-RG 20
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. Collection Management Files, 1929-2005; 167871; 25.38 Linear feet
  - Subseries IV.B. Outgoing Loans, 1939, 1947, 1976-2005; 1976-2002; 109501; 20.21 Linear feet
    - OLR-1993.4. Williams College Museum of Art, 1992-1993; 111815 (Offsite-box 25, Folder unknown container)
      Includes exhibition brochure and checklist.
    - OLR-1993.5. The Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, 1993-1995; 111828 (Offsite-box 26, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1993.6. Fraunces Tavern Museum, 1992-1993; 111818 (Offsite-box 26, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1993.7. The Hudson River Museum (2 folders), 1992-1993; 111819 (Offsite-box 26, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1993.8. The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1993-1995; 111827 (Offsite-box 26, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1992-1994; 111832 (Offsite-box 26, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Williams College, Archives and Special Collections, 1992-1993; 111833 (Offsite-box 26, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Bobst Library, New York University, 1993; 111836 (Offsite-box 26, Folder unknown container)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1993 (2 of 8 folders), 1991-1994; 111847 (Offsite-box 26, Folder unknown container)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1993 (6 of 8 folders), 1991-1994; 111848 (Offsite-box 27, Folder unknown container)
    - Unknown resolutions, 1993, 1993-1994; 112075 (Offsite-box 28, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1994.1. Deputy Mayor's Office, City of New York, 1994-1996; 111851 (Offsite-box 28, Folder unknown container)
      Includes photographic and polaroid photographic prints of the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1994.1. Pictures for Possible Loan, circa 1994; 111940 (Offsite-box 28, Folder unknown container)
      Includes photographic and polaroid photographic prints that appear to be related to the OL-R1994.1 loan.
    - OLR-1994.2. The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1993; 111852 (Offsite-box 28, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1994.3. National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian, 1994-1995; 111853 (Offsite-box 28, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1994.4. National Academy of Design, 111854 (Offsite-box 28, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1994.5. Virginia Historical Society, 111855 (Offsite-box 28, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1994.6. Memorial Art Gallery, University of Rochester (2 folders), 1993-1995; 111856 (Offsite-box 28, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1994.7. Art in Embassies Program, U.S. Department of State (Budapest, Hungary), 1994-1997; 111858 (Offsite-box 28, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1994.8. The Carnegie Museum of Art, 111859 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1994.9. The Hudson River Museum, 1994-1995; 111860 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1994.10. The Jordan-Volpe Gallery, Inc., 111861 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1994.11. The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1993-1994; 111862 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1994.12. Monnaie de Paris, Bibliotheque Nationale, 1993-1995; 111865 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - Long-term loan: Mayor's Office, City of New York, 1994-1995; 111874 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
      Concerns loan of Steamboat 'Thomas E. Hulse' and Steamboat 'Cayuga' by James Bard for display in Mayor's Office. Includes photographic and polaroid photographic prints of the requested item(s).
    - Long-term loan: Executive Mansion, State of New York, 1993-1995; 111918 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - Long-term loan: National Trust for Historic Preservation, Chesterwood, 1990-1994; 111879 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
      Concerns loan of three plaster sculptures by Daniel Chester French: Head of Abraham Lincoln (1954.79), Bust of Edgar Allan Poe (1953.7), and Statue of Ralph Waldo Emerson (1953.14).
    - Long-term loan: Owens-Thomas House, Telfair Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1991-1994; 111878 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - Long-term loan: General, 1990-1994; 111880 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: National Museum of American Art, Smithsonian, 1986-1992; 111872 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: The Brooklyn Museum, 1994; 111938 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: The Trust for Museum Exhibitions, 1993-1994; 111939 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: Hudson River Maritime Museum, 1994; 111951 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: SUNY Binghamton/University of Pennsylvania, 1994; 111952 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Audubon House & Tropical Gardens, 1994; 111866 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Wave Hill, 1994; 111941 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Arts for Transit Division, the Metropolitan Transportation Authority, New York, 1994-1996; 111942 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Museum of Modern Art, 1994-1995; 111943 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Bobst Library, New York University, 1994; 111944 (Offsite-box 29, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The New York Public Library, 1994-1995; 111945 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The New York Public Library, 1994; 111947 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1994, 1991-1994; 111867 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - Loan status summary, 1994, 113887 (Offsite-box 49, Folder unknown container)
      Includes a summary of loans and exhibitions for the period of July 1, 1993 to June 30, 1994.
    - OLR-1995.1. The Rockwell Museum, 1994-1995; 111977 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1995.2. Katonah Museum of Art, 1993-1995; 111978 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1995.3. High Museum of Art, 1994-1996; 111979 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1995.4. The Hudson River Museum, 1995-1996; 111980 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1995.5. The Library of Congress, 1994-1995; 111981 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: Sony Theatres, 1995-1996; 111998 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Office of Manhattan Borough President Ruth Messinger, 1995; 111983 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1994-1996; 111984 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Pierpont Morgan Library, 1995; 111985 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Brandywine River Museum, 1995-1996; 111986 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Athenaeum of Philadelphia, 1994-1995; 111987 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Holley-Williams House, 1995; 111988 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: National Museum of American Art, Smithsonian, 1994-1995; 111993 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The New York Philharmonic Archives, 1994-1995; 111994 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Falvey Library, Villanova University, 1994-1995; 111995 (Offsite-box 30, Folder unknown container)
    - Pending loans, 1995, 1994-1995; 111996 (Offsite-box 31, Folder unknown container)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1995 (3 folders), 1993-1996; 111997 (Offsite-box 31, Folder unknown container)
    - Unknown resolution, 1995, 1994; 112074 (Offsite-box 31, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1996.1. South Street Seaport Museum, 1996-1999; 111999 (Offsite-box 31, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1996.4. Dumbarton House, 112000 (Offsite-box 31, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1996.5. Eaton Fine Art, Inc., 1996-1997; 112001 (Offsite-box 31, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1996.6. The Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco, 1995-1996; 112002 (Offsite-box 31, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1996.7. The Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco, 112003 (Offsite-box 31, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1996.8. Deutsches Historisches Museum, 1995-1996; 112004 (Offsite-box 31, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1996.9. U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development, 1996-1997; 112006 (Offsite-box 31, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1996.10. Macculloch Hall Historical Museum and Gardens, 1992-1997; 112070 (Offsite-box 31, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1996.11. Middlebury College Museum of Art, 1995-1996; 112007 (Offsite-box 32, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1996.12. Mount Holyoke College Art Museum, 1995-1996; 112008 (Offsite-box 32, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1996.13. The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1995-1996; 112071 (Offsite-box 33, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1996.14. The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1990-1996; 112009 (Offsite-box 32, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1996.15. North Carolina Museum of Art, 1995-1997; 112020 (Offsite-box 32, Folder unknown container)
      Includes an exhibition press kit with color slides.
    - OLR-1996.16. Virginia Historical Society, 1995-1996; 112021 (Offsite-box 32, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1996.17. National Building Museum, 112022 (Offsite-box 32, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1996.18. Clermont State Historic Site, 1995-1997; 112023 (Offsite-box 32, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-R1996.19. Knoedler & Company, 1996-1997; 112024 (Offsite-box 32, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: The Trust for Museum Exhibitions, 1993-1997; 112072 (Offsite-box 32, Folder unknown container)
      Additionally includes documents related to a withdrawn loan request by the Trust for Museum Exhibitions.
    - Library: The J. Paul Getty Museum, 1995-1996; 112031 (Offsite-box 32, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, 1996; 112033 (Offsite-box 33, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian, 1995-2000; 112038 (Offsite-box 33, Folder unknown container)
      Includes a long-term loan of Edgar Allen Poe by Samuel Osgood.
    - Library: Cooper-Hewitt National Design Museum, Smithsonian/PaineWebber Art Gallery (2 folders), 1995-1996; 112032 (Offsite-box 33, Folder unknown container)
      Includes slides documenting conservation work performed by the requesting institution relating to the requested item(s).
    - Library: National Museum of American Art, Smithsonian, 1994-1995; 112076 (Offsite-box 33, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Museum of the City of New York, 1996; 112077 (Offsite-box 33, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Mead Art Museum, Amherst College, 1996; 112078 (Offsite-box 33, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: High Museum of Art, 1996-1997; 112079 (Offsite-box 33, Folder unknown container)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1996 (2 folders), 1994-1997; 112027 (Offsite-box 33, Folder unknown container)
      Includes a photographic print of a requesting institution.
    - Unknown resolution, 1996, 1992-1996; 112073 (Offsite-box 33, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1997.2. American Museum of Natural History, 112084 (Offsite-box 33, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1997.3. Berry-Hill Galleries, Inc., 1996-1997; 112729 (Offsite-box 33, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1997.4. Dahesh Museum, 1997-2000; 112092 (Offsite-box 34, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1997.5. Fordham University Law School Library, 112093 (Offsite-box 34, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1997.6. The Frick Art Museum, 1994-1998; 112094 (Offsite-box 34, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1997.7. Fraunces Tavern Museum, 1996-1997; 112095 (Offsite-box 34, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1997.8. Historical Society of Western Pennsylvania, 1997-1999; 112096 (Offsite-box 34, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1997.9. The Jewish Museum, 1996-1997; 112097 (Offsite-box 34, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1997.10. The Mariners' Museum, 1995-1998; 112098 (Offsite-box 34, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1997.11. National Museum of American Jewish Military History, 1997-1998; 112099 (Offsite-box 34, Folder unknown container)
      Includes a polaroid photographic print of the requested item(s).
    - OLR-1997.12. National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian, 1997-2000; 112102 (Offsite-box 34, Folder unknown container)
      Includes photographic prints of the requested item(s) and exhibition checklist.
    - OLR-1997.13. The Parrish Art Museum (2 folders), 1996-1997; 112103 (Offsite-box 34, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1997.14. Tacoma Art Museum, 112104 (Offsite-box 34, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1997.15. Wildlife Conservation Society, 112105 (Offsite-box 35, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: Pfizer Corporation, 1996-1997; 112112 (Offsite-box 35, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: The American Federation of the Arts, 1997; 112115 (Offsite-box 35, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: South Carolina State Museum, 1996-2000; 112676 (Offsite-box 35, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Museums at Hartwick College, 1997-1998; 112107 (Offsite-box 35, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: American Museum of Natural History, 1996-1997; 112108 (Offsite-box 35, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Rosenbach Museum and Library, 1997; 112109 (Offsite-box 35, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: National Archives, Northeast Region, 1997; 112110 (Offsite-box 35, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The New York Academy of Medicine, 1997-1998; 112111 (Offsite-box 35, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Miriam and Ira D. Wallach Art Gallery, Columbia University, 1996-1998; 112114 (Offsite-box 35, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Centre Georges Pompidou, 1996-1998; 112116 (Offsite-box 35, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Museum of Jewish Heritage, 1996-1998; 112117 (Offsite-box 35, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Hayward Gallery (2 folders), 1997-1998; 112118 (Offsite-box 35, Folder unknown container)
      Includes exhibition education packet and brochure.
    - Library: Broadway Theatre Institute, 1997; 112148 (Offsite-box 35, Folder unknown container)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1997, 1997-1998; 112141 (Offsite-box 36, Folder unknown container)
    - Unknown resolution, 1997, 112144 (Offsite-box 36, Folder unknown container)
      Includes photographic prints of a requesting institution.
    - OLR-1998.1. The Navy Museum, Department of the Navy, 1996-1998; 112149 (Offsite-box 36, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1998.2. National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian, 1997-2000; 112150 (Offsite-box 36, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1998.2. The Equitable Gallery, 1997-1998; 112151 (Offsite-box 36, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1998.3. Canton Museum of Art/Timken Museum of Art, 1998-1999; 112152 (Offsite-box 36, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1998.3. Fraunces Tavern, 1998-2001; 112153 (Offsite-box 36, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1998.4. Art in Embassies Program, U.S. Department of State (London, United Kingdom), 1997-2000; 112154 (Offsite-box 36, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1998.5. Abigail Adams Smith Museum, 1998-1999; 112155 (Offsite-box 36, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1998.5. The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 112156 (Offsite-box 36, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1998.6. Museum of American Folk Art, 1995-1998; 112160 (Offsite-box 36, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1998.7. The Museums at Stony Brook, 1998-1999; 112161 (Offsite-box 36, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1998.8. Crocker Art Museum, 1997-1998; 112162 (Offsite-box 36, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1998.125. Fraunces Tavern Museum, 1998-2000; 112163 (Offsite-box 36, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: Dallas Museum of Art, 1997-1999; 112167 (Offsite-box 36, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: Art in Embassies Program, U.S. Department of State (Rome, Italy), 1998-2000; 112168 (Offsite-box 37, Folder unknown container)
      Includes the catalogue for the Art in Embassies Collection of Villa Taverna.
    - Library: Canadian Centre for Architecture, 1997-1998; 112166 (Offsite-box 37, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Brandywine River Museum, 1998-1999; 112170 (Offsite-box 37, Folder unknown container)
      Includes the exhibition brochure.
    - Library: Guild Hall of East Hampton, 1998-2000; 112171 (Offsite-box 37, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Hunter Galleries, Hunter College, 1997-1998; 112172 (Offsite-box 37, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Museum of Contemporary Art, 1997-2000; 112173 (Offsite-box 37, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Nassau County Museum of Art, 1998-1999; 112174 (Offsite-box 37, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Museum of the City of New York, 1998; 112175 (Offsite-box 37, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Fales Library, New York University, 1998; 112180 (Offsite-box 37, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The New York Public Library (2 folders), 1997-1998; 112181 (Offsite-box 37, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Douglas F. Cooley Memorial Art Gallery, Reed College, 1997-1998; 112182 (Offsite-box 37, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Oakland Museum, 1997-1999; 112183 (Offsite-box 37, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Canadian Centre for Architecture, 1996-1998; 112184 (Offsite-box 37, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Grolier Club, 1997-1998; 112185 (Offsite-box 37, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Cooper-Hewitt National Design Museum, Smithsonian, 1997-1998; 112187 (Offsite-box 38, Folder unknown container)
    - Unfulfilled loans, 1998, 112188 (Offsite-box 38, Folder unknown container)
    - Unknown resolution, 1998, 112189 (Offsite-box 38, Folder unknown container)
    - Miscellaneous loan documents, 1994-1998, 113908 (Offsite-box 48, Folder unknown container)
      Contains various assorted documents, including a list of long-term loans as of 1994, a 1996 Receipt for Outgoing Material from the Connecticut Historical Society documenting the arrival of a box created by The Duofold Health Underwear Co. of Mohawk, New York and a 1998 incoming loan of Bust of Paul Robeson by Jacob Epstein.
    - OUT-1999.1. Art in Embassies Program, U.S. Department of State (Helsinki, Finland), 1999-2000; 112194 (Offsite-box 38, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1999.1. Museum for Kunst und Gewerbe Hamburg, 1998-1999; 112195 (Offsite-box 38, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.2. Art in Embassies Program, U.S. Department of State (Netherlands), 1999-2000; 112196 (Offsite-box 38, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1999.2. The Lincoln Museum, 1998-1999; 112197 (Offsite-box 38, Folder unknown container)
    - OLR-1999.4. Osterreichische Galerie, 1998-1999; 112198 (Offsite-box 38, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.5. The Brooklyn Museum, 1996-2000; 112199 (Offsite-box 38, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.7. The Hudson River Museum of Westchester, 112200 (Offsite-box 38, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.8. Folger Shakespeare Library, 1999-2000; 112201 (Offsite-box 38, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.9. Brandywine River Museum, 112202 (Offsite-box 38, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.10. Fraunces Tavern Museum, 112203 (Offsite-box 38, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.11. Tate Britain (1 of 2), 1997-2002; 112736 (Offsite-box 38, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.11. Tate Britain (2 of 2), 1997-2002; 112754 (Offsite-box 39, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.12. The Museums at Stony Brook, 112855 (Offsite-box 39, Folder unknown container)
      Includes polaroid photographic prints of a sculpture labeled 1936.660.
    - OL-1999.13. Yale University Art Gallery, 1999-2001; 112764 (Offsite-box 39, Folder unknown container)
      Includes polaroid photographic prints relating to packing of the requested item(s).
    - OL-1999.15. Virginia Historical Society, 1999-2000; 112843 (Offsite-box 39, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.19. National Gallery of Art, Smithsonian, 1999-2000; 112204 (Offsite-box 39, Folder unknown container)
      Includes photographic slides of requested item(s).
    - OL-1999.20. National Museum of American Art, Smithsonian, 1997-1999; 112205 (Offsite-box 39, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.21. National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian, 1997-1999; 112217 (Offsite-box 39, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.22. The Connecticut Historical Society, 1998-2006; 113948 (Offsite-box 49, Folder unknown container)
      Concerns a long-term loan of L.1952.2 Armchair, 1680-1720, Maple, ash from 1998 to 2006.
    - OL-1999.23. Stanford University Museum of Art, 1997-1999; 112218 (Offsite-box 39, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.24. The Museum of Modern Art, 112219 (Offsite-box 39, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.27. Arts and Communications (Canada Trust), 1998; 112220 (Offsite-box 39, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.28. The Trust for Museum Exhibitions, 1999-2000; 112868 (Offsite-box 39, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.29. Buffalo Bill Historical Center (2 folders), 1999-2001; 112221 (Offsite-box 40, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.30. Nassau County Museum of Art, 1999-2000; 112222 (Offsite-box 40, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.31. The Baltimore Museum of Art, 1998-2000; 112223 (Offsite-box 40, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.39. The Barnum Museum, 1999-2000; 112290 (Offsite-box 40, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.40. Art in Embassies Program, U.S. Department of State (London, UK), 1999-2000; 112291 (Offsite-box 40, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.41. The Metropolitan Museum of Art (3 of 4 folders), 1999-2001; 112293 (Offsite-box 40, Folder unknown container)
      Includes a polaroid photographic print documenting damage to the requested item(s).
    - OL-1999.41. The Metropolitan Museum of Art (1 of 4 folders), 1999-2001; 112877 (Offsite-box 41, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.42. Staten Island Institute of Arts and Sciences, 1999-2000; 112294 (Offsite-box 41, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.43. Gibbes Museum of Art, 1999-2000; 112295 (Offsite-box 41, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.44. Ellis Island Immigration Museum, 112296 (Offsite-box 41, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.45. Yale University Art Gallery, 1999-2002; 112881 (Offsite-box 41, Folder unknown container)
    - OL-1999.46. National Academy of Design (2 folders), 1999-2001; 112298 (Offsite-box 41, Folder unknown container)
    - Museum: The Union League Club, 1998-1999; 112311 (Offsite-box 41, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Society for the Preservation of Long Island Antiquities, 1996-1999; 112317 (Offsite-box 41, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Museums at Stony Brook, 1999; 112318 (Offsite-box 41, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Whitney Museum of American Art, 1998-1999; 112319 (Offsite-box 41, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Powerhouse Museum, 1997-1998; 112320 (Offsite-box 41, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Museum of the City of New York, 1998; 112321 (Offsite-box 41, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: The Museums at Stony Brook, 1997-1999; 112350 (Offsite-box 42, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Miriam and Ira D. Wallach Art Gallery, Columbia University, 1999-2000; 112373 (Offsite-box 42, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Schomberg Center for Research in Black Culture, 1999-2000; 112384 (Offsite-box 42, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Putnam County Historical Society, 1999-2000; 112385 (Offsite-box 42, Folder unknown container)
    - Library: Museum Presentation Associates/Cincinnati Art Museum, 1999-2000; 113995 (Offsite-box 49, Folder unknown container)
      See also folder Library: Museum Presentation Associates/The Long Island Museum (2001).